vacationquests.com 2015-12-21

# Vacation Quests | Privacy policy

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

**Parental Discretion**

HowToTravel.info is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to use the site, provide any personal information or receive our email distributions. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s)or legal guardian(s) before viewing the website.  No one under the age of 21 is allowed to receive our emails.

**Third Party Advertising**

Some of the ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by our web advertising partners. Information about your visit to their site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you.

**Tracking & Third Party Cookies**

You may have read about “cookies” or bits of information that are placed by a Website in a storage place on your own computer. As with most other Web sites, the HowToTravel.info does use cookies but only to allow us to quickly check your status as a subscriber and facilitate access to your preferences. Some of our advertisers may serve you cookies as well. Unfortunately, we do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. If you don’t want cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them.

**Links To Other Sites**

As part of the service, HowToTravel.info may create links allowing you to access third party sites. HowToTravel.info is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites’ individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

Scroll to top
